[
    {
      "question": "What is the  2?<br> (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "12.56",
      "options": [
        "14.06",
        "15.56",
        "12.56",
        "11.06"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 7? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "153.86",
      "options": [
        "152.36",
        "156.86",
        "155.36",
        "153.86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 10? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "314.0",
      "options": [
        "317.0",
        "314.0",
        "312.5",
        "315.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 3? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "28.26",
      "options": [
        "28.26",
        "31.26",
        "26.76",
        "29.76"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 10? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "314.0",
      "options": [
        "317.0",
        "315.5",
        "312.5",
        "314.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 10? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "314.0",
      "options": [
        "312.5",
        "315.5",
        "317.0",
        "314.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 6?<br> (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "113.04",
      "options": [
        "114.54",
        "111.54",
        "116.04",
        "113.04"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 1?<br> (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3.14",
      "options": [
        "6.14",
        "3.14",
        "4.64",
        "1.64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle with radius 7?<br> (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "153.86",
      "options": [
        "152.36",
        "156.86",
        "153.86",
        "155.36"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle with radius 7?<br> (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "153.86",
      "options": [
        "153.86",
        "155.36",
        "156.86",
        "152.36"
      ]
    }
]